{
    "id": "1",
    "name": "13 Times Table",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "13 x 1 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "13"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 2 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "26"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 3 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "39"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 4 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "52"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 5 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "65"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 6 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "78"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 7 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "91"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 8 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "104"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 9 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "117"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 10 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "130"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 11 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "143"
        },
        {
            "question": "13 x 12 = ?",
            "correctAnswer": "156"
        }
    ]
}